[
    {
        "question": "What is the equation for Ohm's Law?",
        "options": [
            "V = I/R",
            "V = IR",
            "V = I - R",
            "V = I^2"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these mistakes will NOT generate a near infinite current?",
        "options": [
            "Supplying 1 V to a circuit with near 0 resistance",
            "Suppling a near infinite voltage to a circuit with a 100 Ohm resistor",
            "Installing an ideal voltmeter in series",
            "Installing an ideal ammeter in parallel"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following branches has the LEAST amount of effective resistance?",
        "options": [
            "A single 100 Ohm resistor",
            "Two 50 Ohm resistors in series",
            "Two 50 Ohm resistors in parallel",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the effective resistance of an open switch in series?",
        "options": [
            "infinite",
            "0",
            "Depends on the voltage supplied",
            "Wrong answer"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "If two resistors are in parallel and the potential difference across the first is 10 V, what is the potential difference across the second?",
        "options": [
            "Unknown",
            "0 V",
            "5 V",
            "10 V"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you determine power dissipated by a resistor given its resistance and the current across it?",
        "options": [
            "P=IR",
            "P=(I^2)R",
            "P=I/R",
            "P=(I^2)/R"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "If two 10 V batteries facing the SAME direction are placed end-to-end in series, what is the effective voltage they can supply to a circuit?",
        "options": [
            "0 V",
            "10 V",
            "20 V",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "If two 10 V batteries facing DIFFERENT directions are placed end-to-end in series, what is the effective voltage they can supply to a circuit?",
        "options": [
            "0 V",
            "10 V",
            "20 V",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a circuit consists of a 1 W lightbulb powered by a 10 V battery, what would happen if a second 1 W lightbulb is added in parallel?",
        "options": [
            "The first lightbulb gets brighter.",
            "The first lightbulb's brightness is unaffected.",
            "The first lighbulb gets dimmer.",
            "The first lightbulb turns off entirely."
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 1+1?",
        "options": [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    }
]
